publicmutualonline.com.my 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy Statement ("the Privacy Policy Statement") governs Public Mutual on the Internet (www.publicmutual.com.my) and Public Mutual Online (www.publicmutualonline.com.my) offered by Public Mutual Berhad (PMB).

The Customer's personal information is collected in order to avail the Customer of the PMB’s Internet services (www.publicmutual.com.my) and Public Mutual Online (www.publicmutualonline.com.my) and to enable Customer to enjoy access to other online services offered by the Public Mutual Berhad. The Customer herewith refers to online registrants and/or customers who have or had invested with Public Mutual Berhad.  This Privacy Policy Statement is issued to reinforce the PMB’s commitment to the policy of protecting at all times the confidentiality, integrity and security of the information provided by Customer to PMB.

 **1\. SECURITY OF INFORMATION**

SECURITY PROCEDURES IN PLACE TO PROTECT THE CUSTOMER'S INFORMATION

Public Mutual Bhd is committed to using its best endeavours to maintain high computer security standards and procedures in order to ensure that all information provided by the Customer are secure and confidential at all times. To this end, PMB has in place the required control systems to ensure security and confidentiality of the Customer's information at all times. These security standards and procedures shall be maintained notwithstanding that the company-customer relationship may have been terminated or otherwise ended. Nevertheless PMB hereby expressly advises the Customer that the PMB does not have control over the computer, computer software, systems and other incidentals used by the Customer to access the 

www.publicmutual.com.my and Public Mutual Online (www.publicmutualonline.com.my) on this website and further that transmission over the Internet cannot be guaranteed, warranted or represented to be absolutely secure.

**2\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

In accordance with strict compliance to Guidelines by Securities Commission, and apart from the sharing of information between authorized persons of PMB such as licensed unit trust agents, institutional agents and/or Public Bank Group, PMB will not disclose the Customer's information to any third party or external organizations without prior consent.   If the Customer does not wish to have the Customer's information shared with any other party, or the Customer does not wish to be solicited for products or services offered by PMB or parties it provides information to, please write in to the PMB at the address below:

**e-Marketing Unit**  
Marketing & Financial Planning Department  
                                         Public Mutual Berhad                                        

 Menara Public Bank 2  
No.78, Jalan Raja Chulan  
50200 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia  
Email : [mktg@publicmutual.com.my](mailto:mktg@publicmutual.com.my)

The instances where PMB will disclose the Customer information are:   

a) where it is required by law, Court Order or is otherwise legally permitted;

b) where such disclosure is required under Order of Court, legislation or regulations to be divulged to any government agency, agencies, ministries, departments or bodies established or approved by Securities Commission;

c) where requested or permitted by the Customer in writing.

**3\. COLLECTION AND USE OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION**

Certain personal information of the Customer as particularised by PMB from time to time will be required to be submitted to the PMB by the Customer to enable PMB to process the Customer's request for information pertaining to services offered by PMB for handling queries, evaluating Customer’s investment needs and/or offering PMB’s products and services. Generally, the nature of information that is required includes but shall not be limited to information such as Customer's name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, age, gender, particulars of identity documents such as identity card or passport and where applicable, financial information such as information of income, assets, liabilities for the purpose of financial planning services as PMB shall require from time to time.   Although the primary purpose of acquiring the information is to confine its use to the normal course of the general business between PMB and its Customer, the said information may also be applied for purposes incidental to and connected with the said primary purpose including the provision of www.publicmutual.com.my as well as to evaluate the Customer's needs that may arise from time to time, to enable PMB to facilitate the provision of information pertaining to the PMB's products and services available from time to time.

**4\. CUSTOMER'S QUESTIONS OR COMPLAINTS**

Any questions or complaints relating to the PMB's handling of personal information may be made to:

**e-Marketing Unit**  
Marketing & Financial Planning Department  
                      Public Mutual Berhad                     

Menara Public Bank 2  
No.78, Jalan Raja Chulan  
50200 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia  
Email : [mktg@publicmutual.com.my](mailto:mktg@publicmutual.com.my)
